<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Common words -->
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="content">Content</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="identification">Your Identification</string>
    <string name="polls">Votes</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="participants">Participants</string>
    <string name="vote_singular">vote</string>
    <string name="vote_plural">votes</string>
    <string name="empty_vote">Blank vote</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>

    <!-- Activities -->
    <string name="notification">A vote is currently running. Tap to bring in front.</string>
    <string name="poll_archive">Vote Archive</string>
    <string name="cast">Cast Vote</string>
    <string name="cast_votes">Cast votes: %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="poll_start_time">Start date</string>
    <string name="number_voters">Eligible voters</string>
    <string name="number_cast_votes">Cast votes</string>
    <string name="participation">Participation</string>
    <string name="result_chart">Result Chart</string>
    <string name="archived_votes">Archived Votes</string>
    <string name="no_archived_votes">There are currently no archived votes</string>
    <string name="no_votes">There are currently no votes</string>
    <string name="allow_empty_vote">Allow blank votes</string>
    <string name="no_options">There are currently no options</string>

    <!-- Network -->
    <string name="network_name">Network name</string>
    <string name="network_key">Network key</string>
    <string name="network_info">Network information</string>
    <string name="not_connected">No network set up</string>
    <string name="networks">Network Connection for Voting</string>
    <string name="dialog_wait_wifi">Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="button_use_actual_ssid">Use network \"%1$s\"</string>
    <string name="button_scan_nfc">Scan NFC tag</string>
    <string name="advance_network_config">Advanced network configuration</string>
    <string name="write_nfc_tag">Write NFC tag</string>
    <string name="put_nfc">Put an NFC tag in proximity of your device&#8230;</string>
    <string name="create_new_network">Create network</string>
    <string name="network_wlan_key">WLAN Key</string>
    <string name="capture_qrcode">Scan QR-code</string>
    <string name="join_network">Join electorate</string>
    <string name="group_password_desc">Group password</string>
    <string name="group_name_desc">Group number</string>
    <string name="network_password">Password</string>
    <string name="recreate_network">Modify</string>
    <string name="tap_nfc_tag">Please tap a writeable NFC Tag on the back of your device</string>
    

    <!-- Action bar titles -->
    <string name="action_redo_poll">Repeat vote</string>
    <string name="action_clone_poll">Clone vote</string>
    <string name="action_create_poll">Create new vote</string>
    <string name="action_start_poll">Start vote</string>
    <string name="action_next">Next</string>
    <string name="action_stop_poll">Finish vote</string>
    <string name="action_start_poll_period">Start Voting Period</string>

    <!-- Question Dialogs -->
    <string name="dialog_title_confirm_vote">Confirm your vote?</string>
    <string name="dialog_confirm_vote">
<![CDATA[
			You have selected the following option:<br /><br /><b>%1$s</b><br /><br />Do you want to confirm your choice and send your vote?"
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_title_save_poll">Save the vote?</string>
    <string name="dialog_save_poll">Do you want to save the modifications you have done on this vote?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_stop_poll">Finish the vote?</string>
    <string name="dialog_stop_poll">Some participants have not voted yet. Do you really want to finish the voting phase?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_add_option">Add option in edition?</string>
    <string name="dialog_add_option">You still have an option in edition. Do you want to add it to the vote?</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_back">Quit?</string>
    <string name="dialog_back">By going back, you won\'t be able to participate to the vote. Do you really want that?</string>
    <string name="dialog_back_admin">By going back, you won\'t be able to administrate the vote. You will have to restart the procedure from the beginning. Do you really want that?</string>
    <string name="dialog_back_result">By going back, you won\'t be able to see result of the vote. Do you really want that?</string>

    <!-- Error or Info Dialogs / Toast -->
    <string name="toast_scroll">Please first have a look at all options</string>
    <string name="toast_choose_one_option">Please choose one of the given options</string>
    <string name="toast_join_error_admin">A group with the same name already exists! Please choose another name!</string>
    <string name="toast_join_error_voter">No group with the given name exists. Please wait for the administrator to create the group.</string>
    <string name="toast_join_error">Error creating/joining the group!</string>
    <string name="toast_join_error_voter_network">Error joining the group! It seems there is a problem with your network card. Please try to disable the wifi and enable it again.</string>
    <string name="toast_join_error_invalid_name">Invalid group name! Please choose another name!</string>
    <string name="toast_network_connection_error">Failed to connect to network!</string>
    <string name="toast_redo_impossible">An error occurred while trying to restart the vote.</string>
    <string name="toast_wifi_is_not_connected">You are not currently connected to a wireless network. Please choose another option.</string>
    <string name="toast_wifi_is_disabled">Wifi is currently disabled. Please enable it first.</string>
    <string name="toast_network_lost">You have been disconnected from the network.</string>
    <string name="toast_question_empty">Question cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="toast_not_enough_options">There must be at least two options.</string>
    <string name="toast_option_empty">Options cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="toast_not_enough_participant_selected">Please select at least two participants.</string>
    <string name="toast_not_everybody_accepted">Not every body has accepted the vote. Wait or exclude the concerned people from the electorate.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_no_identification">No identification set</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_identification">You did not enter an identification. Please first do that.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_attack_detected">Attack detected !!</string>
    <string name="dialog_attack_impersonalization">An attack has been detected! Someone is trying to impersonate a group member in order to be able to vote in his name. We strongly recommand to interrupt the vote session and start a new session.</string>
    <string name="dialog_attack_different_senders">An attack has been detected! Someone has sent a message on behalf of another member of the group. We strongly recommand to interrupt the vote session and start a new session.</string>
    <string name="dialog_attack_different_salts">An attack has been detected! Someone is sending different cryptographic values. The vote must be interrupted. Create a new group and give the password only to people allowed to vote.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_result_chart">Result Chart</string>
    <string name="dialog_not_included_title">Your are not in the electorate</string>
    <string name="dialog_not_included">You were not included in the electorate. So, you cannot participate to the vote. You will be redirected to the main screen.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_network_lost">Group connection lost!</string>
    <string name="dialog_network_lost">The group connection has been lost. The vote will be interrupted.</string>
    <string name="dialog_network_not_found">Network not found</string>
    <string name="dialog_network_not_found_text">The network \"%1$s\" is not available, cannot connect.</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_wrong_key">Wrong group password!</string>
    <string name="dialog_wrong_key">You probably indicated a wrong group password! Please go back and try to reconnect to the group.</string>

    <!-- Help overlays -->
    <string name="overlay_close">Touch the screen to close this help</string>
    <string name="overlay_identification">Put your identification here&#8230;</string>
    <string name="overlay_network_option">&#8230; then choose a method to join the network where the vote session takes place.</string>
    <string name="overlay_review">Check the content&#8230;</string>
    <string name="overlay_review_ok">&#8230; and press the button if you agree with it.</string>
    <string name="overlay_previous_screen">Use this button to return to previous screen.</string>

    <!-- Activity titles -->
    <string name="voter_app_app_name">MobiVote</string>
    <string name="title_activity_check_electorate">Check electorate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wait_for_votes">Waiting&#8230;</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vote">Vote</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_terminated_polls">Vote Archive</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display_result">Vote Results</string>
    <string name="title_activity_network_informations">Network Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create_network">Create a network</string>
    <string name="title_activity_poll">Vote Administration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_network_config">Network Configuration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_poll_detail">Vote Setup</string>
    <string name="title_activity_electorate">Choose electorate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_review_poll">Vote review</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wait_for_votes_admin">Waiting&#8230;</string>

    <!-- Activity subtitles -->
    <string name="subtitle_welcome">Welcome to MobiVote</string>
    <string name="subtitle_check_electorate">Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="subtitle_wait_votes">Thanks for voting!\nWaiting for votes&#8230;</string>
    <string name="subtitle_wait_votes_admin">Thanks for voting!\nWaiting for votes&#8230;</string>

    <!-- Hints in EditText fields -->
    <string name="hint_group_name">Group number</string>
    <string name="hint_group_password">Group Password</string>
    <string name="hint_network_wlan_key">WLAN Key</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_question">Enter the question of the vote here</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_option">Enter the option here</string>

    <!-- Image descriptions -->
    <string name="description_participant_included">Participants included</string>
    <string name="description_network">Network</string>
    <string name="description_participant_avatar">Participant avatar</string>
    <string name="description_accepted">Review accepted</string>
    <string name="description_poll">Vote</string>
    <string name="description_delete_poll">Delete Vote</string>
    <string name="description_option">Option</string>
    <string name="description_add_option">Add option</string>
    <string name="description_qrcode">QR-code</string>

    <!-- Help dialog titles -->
    <string name="help_title_main">Welcome to MobiVote</string>
    <string name="help_title_electorate">Electorate selection</string>
    <string name="help_title_review">Vote review</string>
    <string name="help_title_network_info">Network information</string>
    <string name="help_title_vote">Vote</string>
    <string name="help_title_wait">Vote progress</string>
    <string name="help_title_display_results">Vote result</string>
    <string name="help_title_archive">Vote archive</string>
    <string name="help_title_network_config">Network configuration</string>
    <string name="help_title_poll">Vote creation</string>
    <string name="help_title_poll_details">Vote details</string>

    <!-- NFC Strings -->
    <string name="nfc_success">Success</string>
    <string name="nfc_write_success">NFC tag written successfully</string>
    <string name="nfc_write_failed">NFC tag write failed</string>
    <string name="nfc_readonly">This NFC tag is read only</string>
    <string name="nfc_not_enough_space">This NFC tag doesn\'t have enough free space</string>
    <string name="nfc_unable_format_ndef">Unable to format NFC tag to NDEF</string>
    <string name="nfc_no_ndef_support">This NFC tag doesn\'t appear to support NDEF format</string>
    <string name="nfc_tag_read_failed">Unable to read NFC tag</string>
    <string name="nfc_enable_nfc">Enable NFC</string>
    <string name="nfc_enable_nfc_question">In order to use this feature, NFC must be enabled. Enable now?</string>

    <!-- Help dialog texts -->
    <string name="help_text_main">
<![CDATA[
			This app allows you to set up a vote between people using their smartphone. The vote session takes place over a wifi network.
			<br /><br />
			From this screen, you have three options.
			<ul>
			<li><b>Join electorate:</b> join a vote initiated by another person.</li>
			<li><b>Votes:</b> set up your own vote.</li>
			<li><b>Vote archive:</b> consult old votes to which you participated.</li>
			</ul>
			<br />
			<b>About this app</b>
			<br />This app was created in a Master thesis of a student of the Bern University of Applies Sciences (BFH) affiliated to a research group on e-voting<br/> (see the <a href="http://e-voting.bfh.ch">website</a>).
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_poll">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you can create your own votes</b>. All the votes you have created (but which you didn\'t run) appear on this screen.
			<b>This allows you to prepare a vote that will be run later</b>.
			<br/><br/>
			<ul>
			<li>By clicking on one of the available polls, you will enter in the edition screen, where you will be able to modify the vote or to run it.</li>
			<li>With the button at the bottom of the list of available votes, you can define a new vote.</li>
			<li>The garbage icon allows you to delete a poll.</li>
			</ul>
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_poll_details">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you can define the parameters of the vote.</b>
			<ul>
			<li><b>Question:</b> this is the question to which the voter will have to answer to.</li>
			<li><b>Options:</b> this is the list of answers out of which the voters will have to choose one. You can add an option by entering a text in the field at the bottom of the screen and validating in with the + button. You can remove an option by clicking on the corresponding garbage icon.</li>
			<li><b>Allow blank votes:</b> this checkbox adds or remove an option from the list which represent the "No opinion" vote</li>
			<li><b>Start vote:</b> when you have finished defining the vote, you can either press on the "Start vote" button 
			 (at the bottom of the screen for phone, at the upper right corner on tablets) or go back using the button in the upper left corner, and saving it.
			 When you save it, you will be able to access it again later in order to modify and run it.</li>
			</ul>
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_network_config">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you have to configure the way to connect to the vote session.</b>
			<br/><br/>
			In a first time, you have to indicate your identification (for example your name). The you have to choose which wireless network you want to use. In a third time you have to indicate the group credentials.
			<ul>
				<li><b>If you are administrator of the vote</b>, you only have to indicate the wireless network you want to use. 
				For this purpose, you have two possibilities. Either you can use the curently connected wireless network (button \"Use network x\"), 
				or you can choose the advanced network settings where you can choose the network you want to connect to. 
				You also have the possibility to set up an access point on your device. This will work only with a vote with a few participants.</li>
				<li><b>If you simply want to join an existing session</b>, you have four options:</li>
				<ul>
				<li><b>Use network x:</b> this option allows you to use the network to which you are currently connected.
			 	When clicking on this button, you will have to enter the credentials of the vote session that have been defined on the administrator\'s device.</li>
				<li><b>Scan QR-code:</b> with this option, you just have to scan the QR-code displayed on the administrator\'s device. The connection to the network and the entering of the session credentials will be done automatically.</li>
				<li><b>Scan NFC tag:</b> if your device support NFC technology, you can scan data saved on a NFC tag. The connection to the network and the entering of the session credentials will be done automatically.</li>
				<li><b>Advanced network setting:</b> this options allows you to select another network you want to connect to. When clicking on a network, you will have to enter the key of the selected network (if network is not already known) and the credentials of the vote session that have been defined on the administrator\'s device.</li>	
				</ul>
			</ul>
			
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_network_info">
<![CDATA[
			<b>This screen displays the information about the vote session.</b>
			<ul>
				<li><b>Network name:</b> the wireless network on which the vote session will take place.</li>
				<li><b>Group number:</b> the name of the group.</li>
				<li><b>Group password:</b> the password that must be shared by all members of group.</li>
				<li><b>QR-code:</b> the QR-code containing all these informations that can be scanned by people that want to join the group.</li>
				<li><b>Write NFC tag:</b> if your device support NFC technology, this button will be displayed. It allow to to write the information on a NFc tag that will be read by other people.</li>
				<li><b>Your identification:</b> your name as you defined it.</li>
			</ul>
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_electorate_admin">
<![CDATA[
			In this screen, you, as creator of the vote (also called administrator), <b>have to select the people that will have the right to vote</b>.  
			<br/><br/>
			This screen shows you all the participant that are connected to the network session. With the checkboxes on the right, you can select the participant to whom you want to give the right to vote.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_review_admin">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen, you, as administrator, have to wait that every participant agrees with the content of the vote and the electorate.</b>
			<br/>Once every participant has accepted the content of the vote, you can start the voting period.
			<br/><br/>If a participant does not agree with the content of the vote, you can go back to the edition screen using the button on the top left button.<br/>
			If a participant does not accept the content of the vote just for blocking the vote, you can go back and exclude her from the electorate.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_electorate_voter">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you can see which participants of the group are included in the electorate by the administrator of the vote.</b>
			Once the administrator has selected all the participant he wants, you will be redirected to next screen. 
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_review_voter">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you have to check if the content of the vote is correct.</b> If you agree with it, you can press the red tick button corresponding to your name in the list of participants.
			<br/><br/>
			You especially have to check following things:
			<ul>
				<li>Is the question correct?</li>
				<li>Does the list of options contain all options?</li>
				<li>Is every person that has the right to vote in the participant list?</li>
				<li>Nobody without right to vote should appear in the list!</li>
			</ul>
			If one of this condition is not fulfilled, you should not accept the review and ask the administrator of the vote to modify it.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_vote">
<![CDATA[
			<b>In this screen you have to select the option you want to vote for.</b> When selecting an option, a dialog will be shown asking you to confirm your choice.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_wait_admin">
<![CDATA[
			<b>This screen shows the progress of the vote.</b> In the list of participant you can see who has not voted yet.
			 If someone is not voting (because of phone problem, boycott, or another reason), you, as administrator of the vote can decide to interrupt the vote by pressing on the "Finish vote" button.
			<br/><br/>Once everyone has voted, you will be redirected to the result screen.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_wait_voter">
<![CDATA[
			<b>This screen shows the progress of the vote.</b> In the list of participant you can see who has not voted yet.
			<br/><br/>Once everyone has voted, you will be redirected to the result screen.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_display_results">
<![CDATA[
			<b>This screen displays the result of the vote</b>
			<br/><br/>
			If you were the administrator of this vote and the vote just finished, you can redo the vote by clicking on the "Redo vote" button.
			<br/><br/>
			If you access to this screen through the vote archive, you can clone this vote in order to run it again later.
		]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_text_archive">
<![CDATA[
			<b>This screen shows a list of all vote to which you participated</b>
			<br/><br/>
			When you select a vote in the list, you will be redirected to the screen displaying the result of this vote.
		]]>
    </string>

</resources>